http://www.ennovativetech.com/docs-info/return-policy

QED'S RESPONSE TO COVID-19: We anticipate remaining open and continuing our manufacturing and supply operations during the COVID-19 response period. Because Graco Inc. and its affiliates (including Graco Minnesota Inc., Gema, High Pressure Equipment, White Knight, QED Environmental, Heateflex, Smith Manufacturing, and others), supply the Critical Infrastructure Workforce recognized by the U.S. Department of Homeland Security per the following CISA guidance. Read more
Contact Us  |  Call us: +1 (888) 411-0757
HomeNon-Methanol Sampling
En Core® Sampler InformationEn Core® Sampler Starter KitThe Easy Way to Collect Soil VOC SamplesUsing the En Core® Sampler
Product DescriptionsEn Core® FAQsSample CollectionSampling ProcedureExtrusion ProcedurePerformance DataHold Time ValidationAdditional Hold-Time StudiesField Preservation ToolsTerra Core® Soil Sampler Product InformationEasyDraw Syringe® & PowerStop Handle® Product InformationDocs & InfoDocument ArchiveReturn PolicyEPA SW-846 Method 5035Current NewsCredit ApplicationTerms and ConditionsInteractive Media
En Core® AnimationMoviesWebinars
Current WebinarBest Practices for Soil VOC Sampling Webinar PresentationEn Core® Sampler Webinar PDF PresentationWhere to Buy
Buy OnlineAuthorized ResellersContact Us
Contact UsQED Global
Home
Non-Methanol Sampling
En Core® Sampler Information
En Core® Sampler Starter Kit
The Easy Way to Collect Soil VOC Samples
Using the En Core® Sampler
Effective 01/01/2009
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
Our Commitment To Privacy The Information We Collect How We Use Information Our Commitment To Children's Privacy How To Contact Us
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the En Novative Technologies website. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name Address Email address Phone number (etc.)
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when requesting information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 920-465-3960 or send us an email at via our online contact us form.
Contact
2355 Bishop Circle West Dexter, MI 48130
Phone: +1 (920) 465-3960Local: +1 (734) 995-2547 Toll Free: +1 (888) 411-0757 Fax: +1 (920) 465-3963
QED Global
Products
The En Core® SamplerThe En Core® Sampler Starter KitThe Terra Core® SamplerBuy Online
Support
Document ArchiveEn Core® FAQs
Copyright © 2020 QED Environmental Systems, Inc. QED is a Graco Company.
Privacy Policy
